

# **Contact** +989127195462 (Mobile)

kohzadi\_hossein@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/hossein-kohzadi-bb66b036 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

- C#
- Angular2
- React-Native
- Android Development
- Microsoft SQL Server

### Languages

- English (Professional Working)
- Germany (A2)
- French (B1)
- Persian (mother tongue)

#### Certifications

- Test d'évaluation de français (TEF)
- The Complete React Native and Redux Course
- ATC Android
   Application
   Development
- React Native: Building Mobile Apps
- International English Language Test

# Hossein Kohzadi

Full Stack Developer at Caspco

# Summary

A software engineer with a strong technical background who possesses self-discipline and the ability to work with the minimum of supervision. Able to play a key role throughout the software development / support life cycle of a project to ensure that quality solutions meet business objectives. Possessing a good team spirit, deadline orientated and having the ability to organize and present complex solutions clearly and accurately. Experienced in desktop, web and mobile programming. Extensive experience with relational databases including database design and writing stored procedures. Quick learner with strong analytical and problemsolving skills Ability to communicate effectively at all levels Specialties:

Programming languages: C#.Net, React-Native, Android, T-SQL

UI technology: MVVM, WPF, React.js, Angular.js

Data Access Technologies: ADO.NET, LINQ, Entity

Framework, Nhibernate

Front-End Technologies: Ajax, jQuery, JavaScript, HTML, CSS

Database: Microsoft SQL Server, Stored Procedures, Views,

**Functions** 

**Development Tools:** Microsoft Visual Studio, Team Foundation Server, SVN, Resharper, NuGet

Others: Crystal Report, Object-Oriented design and analysis

#### **Publications**

- Problem solving in preventive maintenance schedule by metaheuristic
- Multi-objective optimization functions to optimize scheduling of preventive maintenance by a bee colony

### Experience

React-Native Developer November 2017 - Present

Tehran Province, Iran

CaspCo Senior Software Developer July 2017 - Present

Tehran Province, Iran

Caspian is a leading company in hardware and software development for banking industry.

They have developed an infrastructure (Lotus) for implementing corebanking solutions.

They also are active in networking solutions for banking environments.

Caspian is a branch Of Parsian Bank. It has approximately 200 employees.

#### Responsibilities and Achievements:

- · Working in an Agile team based on Scrum methodology
- · Developing application software based on user requirements.
- · Participating in developing of Trade Finance sub-systems of Lotus core banking solution.
- · Preparing technical presentations and progress reports.
- · Developing queries based on business requirement (Oracle & SQL Developer).
- · Developing recursive queries for complex reports.
- · Participating in requirement gathering and analysis processes.

Technical Environment: Java, Intellij, Eclipse, Drools Rule Engine, jUnit, TestNG, C#, Visual Studio, Atlassian Jira (Agile), PL\SQL, Oracle Database, Maven.

Arang chimi
Software Project Manager
December 2014 - December 2017 (3 years 1 month)
Tehran, Iran

#### Responsibilities and Achievements:

- · Lead analysis meetings with stakeholders
- Defined system requirement specifications
- Prioritized stakeholder 's requirements and made agreement with client.
- · Prepared proposals

- Defined system consistency between stakeholder needs and legacy system
- Prepared Prototype, designed middle-ware for outward clients such as designing Web Services. Designed Tables, Functions, Process, Indexes, Program specifications
- Document preparation, writing specifications for developing components, using CASE applications (Rational rose products)
- Prepared Use Case Diagram, State Diagram, Activity Diagram, Entity Diagram

Arang Chimi Senior Software Developer December 2014 - July 2017 (2 years 8 months) Tehran, Iran

Enterprise Resource Planning (ERP)

Andisheh Pardazan Saramad Software Project Manager March 2014 - December 2014 (10 months)

Shomaran System
Senior Programmer
September 2012 - October 2013 (1 year 2 months)
Tehran, Iran

#### Responsibilities and Achievements:

- Plan, design, write, modify, integrate and test Web-site related code for web client and server-side application components
- Deliver quality code by applying sound development practices, leveraging test driven development methodology and supporting test automation
- Perform system integration and testing, problem troubleshooting and resolution
- Develop web sites architecture and determine software requirements
- Participate in estimating project efforts and delivery timelines
- Mentor and guide teammates in web technologies
- Provide technical input into web-sites roadmaps, negotiating compromises between business and technical constraints
- Consult with internal clients to develop and document web requirements

• Source, select and organize information for inclusion and design the appearance, layout and flow of the presentation on the web

Paradis Hesab Senior Programmer February 2012 - September 2012 (8 months) Tehran, Iran

Responsibilities and Achievements:

- Feasibility study, identification and analysis of stocks, treasury and financial accounting software with the use of Agile (Scrum) and Unified Process Software;
- Preparing Class Diagram and database design for above mentioned systems;
- Production and maintenance of above-mentioned software with the use of SQL Server 2005, C#;
- Preparation of Sprint Backlog, Product Backlog for above mentioned software;
- Participation in meetings for preparing User Stories required for development of above-mentioned software;
- Production and maintenance of above-mentioned software with the use of SQL Server 2005, WPF, C#;
- Preparing reporting service with the use of SQL Server Reporting Service
- Preparing customized UI Elements such as: Auto Completed Textbox, Gridview, Persian Data Calendar, Advanced Search and ...
- Designing and preparing required services with the use of WCF.

# Education

Islamic Azad University, Science and Research Master's Degree, Computer Software Engineering · (2013 - 2015)

Shamsipour Technical and Vocational Faculty
Bachelor's Degree, Computer Software Engineering · (2005 - 2008)

Iran University of Science and Technology Branch, Arak Associate's Degree, Computer Software Engineering (2003 - 2005)

khajeh nasir toosi High School · (2001 - 2003)